As you saw in the last section,
正如你在上节课所见
this dataset includes view and click actions on the home page of Audacity's site,
这个数据集包括 Audacity 网址主页的浏览和点击行为
from users that were shown the control and experimental versions of the A/B test.
可以显示 A/B 测试控制版本和试验版本的用户
Our task is to analyze these actions to see if there
我们的任务是分析这些行为
was a significant difference in performance for the two versions.
观察两种版本的性能是否存在巨大差异
To do this, let's first compute the click-through rate for each group.
为了做到这一点 我们首先计算各组的点击率
Let's start with the control group.
首先是控制组
We can extract all the actions from the control group like this.
我们像这样抽取控制组的所有行为
Now, to compute the click-through rate,
现在为了计算点击率
we'll divide the number of unique users who actually click
我们用实际点击探索课程按钮的独立访客数量
the Explore courses button by the total number of unique users who viewed the page.
除以浏览页面的独立访客总数量
This gives us a click-through rate of about 28 percent.
这样得到点击率是 28%
Let's do the same thing for the experiment group.
对试验组也采用相同的方法
Again, we'll take all the click actions,
我们再次抽取所有点击动作
get the unique number of users,
得到用户的唯一数
and divide that number by the number of unique users who viewed the page.
并用这个数除以浏览页面的独立访客数量
That gives us a click-through rate of about 31 percent.
这样得到点击率是 31%
So in this sample, the experiment group's click-through rate was
因此在这个样本中 试验组点击率
higher than the control group's click-through rate by about 3 percent.
比控制组点击率高出 3%
Now that we know the observed difference in this sample,
既然了解到样本中的明显差别
we have to see if this difference is significant and not just due to chance.
我们需要了解这个差异是显著的 而不是因为偶然
Let's bootstrap the sample to simulate
我们利用引导指令输入样本
the sampling distribution for the difference in proportions.
模拟抽样分布的比例差
Let's take a look at our sampling distribution.
我们先看一下抽样分布
If you remember from the previous lesson,
如果你记得之前课程
we can compute the p-value for our statistic which is
我们计算统计量中的 p 值
the observed difference in proportions by simulating
即通过模拟零假设情况中的分布
the distribution under the null hypothesis and then
得到的显著比例差
finding the probability that our statistic came from this distribution.
然后根据这个分布得到统计量的概率
To simulate from the null,
为了模拟零假设
we'll create a normal distribution centered at zero,
我们创建一个以 0 为中心的正态分布
with the same standard deviation as our sampling distribution we simulated here.
标准差与我们模拟的抽样分布相同
We could see the null distribution here.
我们可以看到这里的零分布
And this is where our observed statistic falls.
这是我们观察统计量的地方
We can't find the p-value like this as these are
我们找不到这样的 p 值
all the null values that are more extreme than our statistic in favor of our alternative.
因为这些空值比支持备择假设的统计量更加极端
With a p-value of approximately a half of percent,
得到的 P 值为百分之一的一半
the difference in click-through rates for the control and
控制组和试验组点击率的差异
experiment groups does appear to be significant.
看起来非常显著
We can reject the null hypothesis,
我们可以拒绝零假设
and based on these results,
并且根据这些结果
it looks like Audacity should launch the new version of the home page.
Audacity 应当发布主页的新版本